1. openBrowser("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
13. delay(1)
17. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your email address", false)
21. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your password", false)
25. delay(2)
29. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
33. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Password field"), "")
37. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
41. delay(2)
45. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your password", false)
49. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
53. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Password field"), "Password2")
57. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
61. delay(2)
65. verifyTextPresent("Download our Mobile App", false)
69. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "vivek.jaiswal")
73. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
77. delay(2)
81. verifyTextPresent("Invalid email address entered", false)
85. closeBrowser()
89. navigateToUrl("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
93. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "assa@gmail.com")
97. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Password field"), "P@ssword2")
101. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
105. delay(5)
109. verifyTextPresent("Invalid login details entered", false)
113. closeBrowser()
117. navigateToUrl("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
121. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
125. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Password field"), "P@ssword1")
129. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
133. delay(2)
137. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Sign Out"), 0)
141. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Sign Out"))
145. delay(5)
149. closeBrowser()