1. openBrowser("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Email address field"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
13. setText(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Password field"), "P@ssword1")
17. click(findTestObject("MVC Login page/Login Button"))
21. delay(2)
25. verifyTextPresent("My Activity Feed", false)
29. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
33. delay(2)
37. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
41. selenium.click("xpath=(.//*[normalize-space(text()) and normalize-space(.)='UKCAT'])[2]/following::li[1]")
45. selenium.click("xpath=(.//*[normalize-space(text()) and normalize-space(.)='UKCAT'])[2]/following::li[2]")
49. selenium.click("xpath=(.//*[normalize-space(text()) and normalize-space(.)='UKCAT'])[2]/following::li[3]")
53. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Home Tab"), 0)
57. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/CPD Tab"), 0)
61. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Managed Accounts Tab"), 0)
65. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Partner Centre Tab"), 0)
69. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Partner Admin Tab"), 0)
73. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Help Tab"), 0)
77. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/My Profile Link"), 0)
81. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Sign Out"), 0)
85. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Choose Questions Sub Tab"), 0)
89. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Mock Tests Sub Tab"), 0)
93. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Group Learning Tab"), 0)
97. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Revision Advice Tab"), 0)
101. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Tags Tab"), 0)
105. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Learning Journal Tab"), 0)
109. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Performance Tab"), 0)
113. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Start your revision session"), 0)
117. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Group Learning"), 0)
121. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Mock Tests"), 0)
125. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button My Performance"), 0)
129. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Forward Arrow"), 0)
133. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Back arrow"), 0)
137. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Details text"), 0)
141. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Questions Answered details"), 0)
145. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Count of Questions Details"), 0)
149. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Resource dropdown"), 0)
153. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Count of Questions Details"), 0)
157. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Count of Questions Details"), 0)
161. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Count of Questions Details"), 0)
165. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Home Tab"))
169. delay(2)
173. verifyTextPresent("My Activity Feed", false)
177. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
181. delay(2)
185. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
189. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/CPD Tab"))
193. delay(2)
197. verifyTextPresent("Our Self Assessment modules will help to keep your knowledge up-to-date and support your continuous professional development.", false)
201. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab"))
205. delay(2)
209. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
213. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Managed Accounts Tab"))
217. delay(2)
221. verifyTextPresent("You do not have any groups associated.", false)
225. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
229. delay(2)
233. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
237. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Partner Centre Tab"))
241. delay(2)
245. verifyTextPresent("PACES build", false)
249. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
253. delay(2)
257. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
261. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Partner Admin Tab"))
265. delay(2)
269. verifyTextPresent("Account Management", false)
273. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
277. delay(2)
281. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
285. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Help Tab"))
289. delay(2)
293. verifyTextPresent("Frequently Asked Questions", false)
297. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
301. delay(2)
305. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
309. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Choose Questions Sub Tab"))
313. delay(2)
317. verifyTextPresent("Choose Questions", false)
321. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab"))
325. delay(2)
329. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
333. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Mock Tests Sub Tab"))
337. delay(2)
341. verifyTextPresent("Please select from one of these Mock Tests:", false)
345. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
349. delay(2)
353. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
357. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Group Learning Tab"))
361. delay(2)
365. verifyTextPresent("Join your peers in this quiz format revision tool and compete against them whilst you test your knowledge.", false)
369. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
373. delay(2)
377. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
381. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Revision Advice Tab"))
385. delay(2)
389. verifyTextPresent("Revision Advice", false)
393. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
397. delay(2)
401. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
405. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Tags Tab"))
409. delay(2)
413. verifyTextPresent("Tagged Questions", false)
417. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
421. delay(2)
425. verifyTextPresent("Exam Revision", false)
429. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Learning Journal Tab"))
433. delay(2)
437. verifyTextPresent("Learning Journal", false)
441. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
445. delay(2)
449. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Start your revision session"))
453. delay(2)
457. verifyTextPresent("Choose Questions", false)
461. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab"))
465. delay(2)
469. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Group Learning"))
473. delay(2)
477. verifyTextPresent("Join your peers in this quiz format revision tool and compete against them whilst you test your knowledge.", false)
481. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
485. delay(2)
489. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button Mock Tests"))
493. delay(2)
497. verifyTextPresent("Please select from one of these Mock Tests:", false)
501. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
505. delay(2)
509. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Button My Performance"))
513. delay(2)
517. verifyTextPresent("Score Analysis", false)
521. click(findTestObject("MVC Exam Revision/Exam Revision Tab - Old"))
525. delay(2)
529. closeBrowser()