1. openBrowser("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
13. delay(1)
17. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your email address", false)
21. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your password", false)
25. delay(2)
29. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
33. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Password_ctl00MainConten"), "")
37. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
41. delay(2)
45. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your password", false)
49. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
53. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Password_ctl00MainConten"), "Password2")
57. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
61. delay(2)
65. verifyTextPresent("Forgot your password or changed your email address?", false)
69. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "vivek.jaiswal")
73. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
77. delay(2)
81. verifyTextPresent("Invalid email address entered", false)
85. closeBrowser()
89. navigateToUrl("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
93. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "assa@gmail.com")
97. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Password_ctl00MainConten"), "P@ssword2")
101. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
105. delay(5)
109. verifyTextPresent("Invalid login details entered", false)
113. closeBrowser()
117. navigateToUrl("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
121. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
125. setText(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Password_ctl00MainConten"), "P@ssword2")
129. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/input_Please enter your passwo"))
133. delay(2)
137. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Page_My Dashboard - BMJ OnExaminati/a_Sign Out"), 0)
141. click(findTestObject("Page_My Dashboard - BMJ OnExaminati/a_Sign Out"))
145. delay(5)
149. closeBrowser()