1. openBrowser("https://testmy.onexamination.com/login.aspx")
5. maximizeWindow()
9. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/a_Forgot your password or chan"))
13. verifyTextPresent("Changed your email address?", false)
17. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
21. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your email address", false)
25. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "    ")
29. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
33. verifyTextPresent("Please enter your email address", false)
37. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "abc")
41. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
45. verifyTextPresent("Invalid email address, please check it is typed correctly", false)
49. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "abc@gmail")
53. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
57. verifyTextPresent("Invalid email address, please check it is typed correctly", false)
61. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "@gmail.com")
65. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
69. verifyTextPresent("Invalid email address, please check it is typed correctly", false)
73. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "a1b2c3@gmail.com")
77. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
81. verifyTextPresent("Please check your email account inbox, the message should arrive within 5 minutes.", false)
85. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/a_Sign In"))
89. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/a_Forgot your password or chan"))
93. setText(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Email address_ctl00MainC"), "vivek.jaiswal@northgateps.com")
97. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/input_Invalid email address pl"))
101. verifyTextPresent("There's been a problem sending your message", false)
105. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/a_Sign In"))
109. click(findTestObject("Page_BMJ OnExamination Sign In/a_Forgot your password or chan"))
113. click(findTestObject("Page_Sign in problems/Page_Sign in problems/a_contact our support team"))
117. verifyTextPresent("Contact Us", false)
121. closeBrowser()